shanghaidaily.com 2006-12-14

# Shanghai Daily | 上海日报 -- English Window to China News

NEWS

OPINION

FEATURES...

BLOG CHANNELS

Supplement

SERVICES

| 

The Shanghai Daily on the Web has adopted the privacy practices with respect to personal information in operating the ShanghaiDaily.com Website as described in this statement (“Privacy Policy”). Our products and services are offered and are made available subject to the terms and conditions set out in this statement. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the User Agreement of ShanghaiDaily.com. We endeavor to continuously assess our privacy practices in light of new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs. Our Privacy Policy may therefore be amended from time to time. You should check our Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are aware of our latest policies.

In this Privacy Policy, you will find the answers to the following questions:

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit the ShanghaiDaily.com Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

**Personal Information You Choose to Provide

Registration Information.

**

You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you register to be a subscriber of ShanghaiDaily.com, register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts. Failure to provide such information may result in our being unable to provide you with our service. You may also provide additional comments on how you see ShanghaiDaily.com servicing your needs and interests. You agree that we may store and deal with any information you provide as part of the registration process or in connection with optional contests, surveys or special offers in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Email Information.**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

**Web Site Use Information**

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small pieces of code called "web beacons" or "clear gifs" to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at [online@ShanghaiDaily.com](mailto:online@ShanghaiDaily.com).

**What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**

As you interact with our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other users in order to tailor the best possible experience for you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with alliances, partnerships or arrangements, we may also provide certain information to third parties if we have determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by a responsible third party. For example, some of our partners operate stores or provide services on our site, while others power offerings developed by us for your use. We also use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing credit card payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

**Notice of New Services and Changes**

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at [unsubscribe@ShanghaiDaily.com](mailto:unsubscribe@ShanghaiDaily.com).

**Links**

Our site contains links to other Internet websites. Since these outside resources are the properties of their respective owners, ShanghaiDaily.com is not responsible for the availability of these sites, as well as their practices, policies, or privacy issues of other sites. We hope you to read their specific policies that might relate to your usage. Links are not intended to imply sponsorship, affiliation or endorsement.

**Personal information disclosure**

In general, we will not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your express consent, but we reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by Chinese law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our Web site.   
There may be other circumstances where we may need to disclose personal information about a user. These are:

  * Employing other companies to perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, providing customer service, sending mail, processing credit card payments, processing currency conversions, or other functions necessary to our business.  

  * If publishers of the products you purchase through our Web site request additional personal information from us. The information practices of those publishers are covered by their own privacy policies.  

  * If we believe that user is harming or interfering with our other users, anyone else, or violating our applicable agreements, or infringing any of our legal rights.  

  * In the event of a sale of all or most of the assets of the company, this information may be transferred to the purchaser.  

| 

Search  
  
---|---|---
